
[
    {
        "identifier": "090bdfea-41f2-4e5f-9d88-d441be583e48",
        "name": "Emoji Cards",
        "cards": [
            {
                "back": "Tears of joy",
                "front": "😂"
            },
            {
                "back": "Expressionless",
                "front": "😑"
            },
            {
                "back": "Disappointed",
                "front": "😞"
            },
            {
                "back": "Confused",
                "front": "😕"
            },
            {
                "back": "Wide open eyes",
                "front": "😳"
            },
            {
                "back": "Party",
                "front": "🥳"
            },
            {
                "back": "Grimacing",
                "front": "😬"
            },
            {
                "back": "Smiling",
                "front": "☺️"
            },
            {
                "back": "Smiling squinting eyes",
                "front": "😊"
            },
            {
                "back": "Thinking",
                "front": "🤔"
            }
        ]
    }
]
